<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jaryn Colbert</title>
    <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jaryn Colbert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 16:20:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sol-itude</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/sol-itude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/sol-itude/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The idea becomes a machine that makes the art.&amp;rdquo; Sol LeWitt
 While at the Recurse Center (RC), I was introduced to the work of Conceptual Artist, Solomon &amp;ldquo;Sol&amp;rdquo; LeWitt. Sol believed that the idea behind the art was more important than its execution. His set of wall drawings were defined as seemingly simple instructions that other artists implemented and brought to life. These instructions were detailed enough to describe the work, while leaving enough ambiguity that ensured each piece would be a bit different each time that it was executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World of Recurse</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/world-of-recurse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/world-of-recurse/</guid>
      <description>The last project that I worked on at the Recurse Center (RC) was a map to display the locations of members of the RC community on an interactive world map.
The front-end was built in JavaScript with React; the map is Leaflet, with the Leaflet MarkerCluster plugin and OpenStreetMap tiles.
The back-end to retrieve data from the RC APIs (RC login required) was written in Python with Flask, and it performs geocoding with the GeoNames geocoder via the GeoPy library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Faces</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/recurse-faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/projects/recurse-faces/</guid>
      <description>To gain experience working on an existing code base, I contributed to Recurse Faces, a flashcard application that helps members of the Recurse Center (RC) community learn the names and faces of their fellow batch mates.
The app was originally created in 2017 by Jason Owen, a talented software developer with whom I had the pleasure of meeting during our stints at RC. I added features to enhance the styling and functionality of the original app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>