<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jaryn Colbert</title>
    <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jaryn Colbert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:08:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jaryncolbert.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:08:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/resume/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 17:08:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jaryn (pronounced like Karen but swap in a &amp;ldquo;J&amp;rdquo;). I&amp;rsquo;m a recent Brooklyn transplant originally from Silver Spring, Maryland. Welcome!
Recent Currently, I am attending the Recurse Center, where I am focused on gaining more experience with front-end technologies. For more info about what I have been up to recently, check out my Now page.
Career I have worked as a software engineer since completing a B.S.E in Computer Engineering at the University of Maryland (Go Terps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>http://jaryncolbert.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jaryncolbert.com/now/</guid>
      <description>I am currently based in Brooklyn, NY attending the Recurse Center, a self-directed educational retreat for programmers looking to improve their skills. While at Recurse, I have been exploring my listening history via the Spotify APIs, recreating the Sol LeWitt&amp;rsquo;s conceptual art pieces with Processing JS, and dabbling in functional programming with Elm. My Recurse batch (Spring 1, &amp;lsquo;19) ends in early May, and I will be pursuing a full-time gig as a software engineer in the greater New York City area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>